commission.bz 2018-09-05

# Privacy Policy | Commission.bz

****We treat all the information we collect with the utmost confidentiality and never will disclose your email to a third party outside of Commission.bz.

Commission.bz will only see information about you if you are on their program and will never pass the information on to a third party.

When we collect personal information about you we will collect this information from you lawfully and fairly and not in any unreasonably intrusive way. You acknowledge and agree that we may collect this information from you in connection with or as a consequence of your use of our site, including, without limitation, the supply of the online services to you. We are the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in any. We collect information from our users at different points on our site. We collect information about you upon registration and we also collect information from any form of correspondence, such as e-mails and telephone conversations, from you or from a third party about you. We may also collect information from you if you choose to partake in special promotions or surveys conducted on our site. We will also collect financial information about you if you choose to obtain payments via ACH or wire transfer. Other information that we collect is outlined below.

**Registration**

In order to use our site, you must first complete the registration form. When you register we collect personal information such as your name, address, email address, telephone and fax numbers. This information is used to contact you about the services on our site and for general correspondence. We also collect additional information (such as “How did you hear about us?”). All information that is mandatory is made known on the registration form and is necessary to complete the registration process. You are encouraged to provide the additional, optional information specified on the registration form so we can provide you with a more personalized relationship.

**External Links**

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such other sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this site.

**Newsletter**

If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter, we ask for contact information such as email addresses. However, it is completely at your discretion to be removed from such a list as set out in our choice and opt-out section below.

**Site and Services Updates**

We also send you site and services announcement updates. You are not able to un-subscribe from these because they contain important information about our site and our services.

**Surveys & Contests**

From time-to-time we request information from you via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose any information to us. Information requested may include contact information (such as email addresses) and demographic information. Survey information will be used for the purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.

**Security**

We take every precaution to prevent the loss, misuse and alteration of all information under our control. When you submit sensitive information via our site, your information is protected both online and off-line. While we use encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. The servers that we store personally identifiable information on are kept in a secure environment. If you have any questions about the security at our site, you can send an email to

**Supplementation of Information**

In order for this site to properly fulfil its obligation to our customers, it is necessary for us to supplement the information we receive with information from third party sources. We send all new members a welcoming email to verify password and username. Established members will occasionally receive information on our clients, services and a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users, our users have the option not receive these types of communications (refer to our choice and opt-out section below).

**Correction/Updating Personal Information:**

If your personally identifiable information changes (such as your email address), or if you no longer desire to use our services, you may correct, update or remove your personal data provided to us. This can be done at the member information page or by emailing our Customer Support at support@commission.bz.

**Choice/Opt-out**

If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter, information about products and services, surveys, or promotional materials from us you may opt-out of receiving these communications by following the unsubscribe instructions in the relevant email or by visiting the “Change Details” page.

**Notification of Changes**

If we decide to change our privacy statement, we will post those changes on our Homepage and in our newsletter so you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If we change the way we use your Personally Identifiable Information we will notify you by email in our newsletter. If you would like to opt out of having your information used in this new manner, we will ask you to contact us within a month and your information will not be used. If you do not contact us within that month, we will assume that you consent to have your information used in this new manner.
